(Raj:)No. Not really.
(Penny:)- Come on, Raj, not even a little bit?
- Not that I can think of.
(Bernadette:)Think harder.
(Raj:)Nope. I guess the heart wants
what the heart wants.
(Raj:)Or in this case, doesn't. I mean, at all.
(Raj:)What?
(Sheldon:)Ye who now will bless the poor
Shall yourselves find blessing
Ba-da-bum!
(Howard:)Done?
(Sheldon:)I think the word you're looking for
is "bravo."
(Leonard:)Okay, you leave the room and find yourself
standing before a pool of melted snowmen.
(Sheldon:)Melted snowmen? Are there carrots
and lumps of coal in the water?
- Uh, what's the difference?
- It's a game of the imagination, Leonard.
(Sheldon:)- Paint a picture.
- Fine. You leave the room and find yourself...